Nothing is harder to track than the truth.
Wind River is a crime, mystery, drama film directed by Taylor Sheridan.
An FBI agent teams with the town's veteran game tracker to investigate a
murder that occurred on a Native American reservation.
Cory Lambert, played by Jeremy Renner.
Jane Banner, played by Elizabeth Olsen.
Martin Hanson, played by Gil Birmingham.
Ben, played by Graham Greene.
Matt Rayburn, played by Jon Bernthal.
Natalie Hanson, played by Kelsey Asbille.
Wind River is a 2017 neo-Western crime film written
and directed by Taylor Sheridan.
It is the third film by Taylor Sheridan on the modern American West.
The film stars Jeremy Renner and Elizabeth Olsen as a U.S.
Fish and Wildlife Service tracker and an FBI agent, respectively, who try to
solve a murder on the Wind River Indian Reservation in Wyoming.
Gil Birmingham, Jon Bernthal, and Graham Greene also star.
Taylor Sheridan has said that he wrote the film to raise awareness of the issue of the high
number of Indigenous women who are raped and murdered, both on and off reservations.
Wind River premiered at the 2017 Sundance Film Festival and was
released in the United States on August 4, 2017.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and was a box office
success, grossing $45 million against an $11 million budget.
It was theatrically released by The Weinstein Company (TWC), but in October 2017, following the reporting of numerous sexual abuse
allegations against Harvey Weinstein, the film's distribution rights for home media were acquired by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of wyoming, usa, rape, gun, fbi, mountain.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.